needtoimpeach.com 2018-11-09

# Privacy Policy - Need to Impeach

## Privacy Policy

Needtoimpeach.com is committed to protecting the privacy of each visitor using its interactive services. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you, as a visitor of Needtoimpeach.com, what types of information we may gather about you when you visit Needtoimpeach.com (the “Web Site”), how we may use that information, and whether we disclose it to anyone. This privacy policy applies only to information collected from you online, not offline. This privacy policy applies only to the Web Site, its subsidiaries and affiliates, but not to other companies’ or organizations’ websites.

If the Web Site decides to change any of its privacy policies, the changes will be posted here so that you will always know the information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom it may be disclosed. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please make sure to check this page periodically for any changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not visit the Web Site.

### 1\. INFORMATION ABOUT ALL VISITORS

The Web Site collects certain information from and about its users in several ways – directly from visitors, from third parties, from our web server logs, and with cookies or other forms of passive data gathering.

User-Supplied Information: There are several areas in the Web Site where we collect personal information from you on a voluntary basis. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable that is not otherwise publicly available, such as your name, address, e-mail address, mailing address, gender, date of birth, or phone numbers. We may collect this information at the following times: (i) when you sign a petition or otherwise sign-up; (ii) when you seek information or apply for services offered through the Web Site and other web sites and (iii) when you provide personal information to us through feedback, survey, or other forms hosted on this Web Site or other websites; and (iv) when you send us an email or otherwise communicate with us.

Server Log Information: When you visit an internet web site, you automatically disclose certain information about yourself, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the time of your visit, and the referring location (e.g., the site or page that offered a link to a page on Needtoimpeach.com). Like many other sites, the Web Site records this basic, non-personally identifiable information about visits to the Web Site.

Cookies and Passive Data Collection: In order to offer and provide customized, personal service, the Website may use cookies to store and help track your information. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive that contains information about the user. The Web Site does not combine information collected through cookies with other personally identifiable information to tell us who you are or even what your username or e-mail address is. If for any reason you wish not to take advantage of cookies, you may have your browser not accept them, although this may disable or render unusable some of the features of the Web Site. Removing or rejecting browser cookies does not necessarily affect third party flash cookies that may be used in connection with our Sites. To delete or disable flash cookies please visit www.adobe.com/proudcts/flashplayer/secuirty for more information.

The Web Site may also collect passive data, such as clickstream data or a user’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, operating system, browser type, time and date of visit, and page views. Clickstream data is a term defined to include a record of clicked selections within the Web Site.

The Web Site may use pixel tags in web pages and certain other content that may read cookies. Similar pixel tags on the Web Site will permit us to count users and collect additional information to improve the content of our Web Site, diagnose problems with our equipment, administer the Web Site, and provide related services.

Although the Web Site seeks to protect your personal information the Web Site cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, an you do so at your own risk.

### 2\. HOW AND WHEN INFORMATION IS USED

We use information in different ways, depending on the type of information:

  * Respond to your inquiry or request;
  * Provide, maintain and improve the Web Site and send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;
  * Provide and deliver information that you request and or that we think will be of interest to you, such as sending you information to keep you informed about various campaigns, candidates, issues, events, and resources;
  * To improve the Web Site and internal operations, including to monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with the Web Site; and
  * Carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.
  * Web Server Logs: This information helps us identify which areas of our site are of interest to our visitors. The Web Site may also collect the IP addresses of its visitors for the purposes of system administration.
  * Cookies: We use cookies to enable you to use our services more easily and to let us keep track of statistical information that helps us improve the Web Site. Cookies also allow us to save preferences for you so that you will not have to re-enter them the next time you visit.

### 3\. LEGAL COMPLIANCE

The Web Site may disclose User Supplied Information in order to: (i) comply with applicable laws; (ii) respond to government inquiries; (iii) comply with valid legal processes; and (iv) protect the rights or property of the Web Site, or Visitors of the Web Site.

### 4\. MINORS

The Web Site adheres to the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and the Federal Trade Commission’s regulations implementing this Act. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from children under thirteen (13) years of age.  The Web Site is intended for use by persons 18 years old or older.  Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use the Web Site.

### 5\. OPTING-OUT

You may register to receive communications from us directly on the Web Site. After you register, we will periodically send you newsletters and other e-mails. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our e-mails. Our e-mail database is continually updated. However, you may continue to receive e-mail communications from us for up to ten business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request.

### 6\. THIRD PARTY LINKS

When you visit a website to which the Web Site provides a link, please be aware that you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy policy. If you choose to obtain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party’s privacy policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

### 7\. GENERALLY

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Accordingly, while we strive to protect your personal information, the Web Site cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, or to or from our online products or services. You transmit all such information at your own risk. However, once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our servers.

Questions regarding the above statement should be directed to (415) 488-6139 for clarification.
